TAHUANA CIRATI

WEB DEVELOPER

- tahuana@gmail.com
- tahuana.com
- **** +1 (416) 428-0567
- **?** Toronto ON Canada
- in tahuana-cirati
- n tahuana

▶ Profile

I am a developer eager for new knowledge and challenges!

I have more than 15 years of working experience in projects playing roles as project analyst, software tester and developer.
Result-driven, attention to detail, and strong analytical skills.
When not coding, I can be

found reading or testing

new delicious recipes.

▶ Skills

LANGUAGES & FRAMEWORKS

JavaScript & Node.js

HTML

CSS

SQL

Ruby on Rails

Express

Bootstrap

Python

DATABASES

MongoDB

PostgreSQL

Oracle

LIBRARIES

jQuery

React

Knex

OTHERS

Project Management
Software Testing
Marketing automation tools

Languages

English

Portuguese

Education

Bridge School

Software Developer Program 2018

Lighthouse Labs

Immersive Full-Stack Web Development Bootcamp 2017

IBMEC Business School

Postgraduate Project Management 2013

UFRJ - Federal University of Rio de Janeiro

Bachelor's Degree Computer Science 2001

Projects

tahuana.com

Aug 2017 to Aug 2017

- My personal website.
- Developed using HTML, CSS and Bootstrap.

Pairwise Jul 2017 to Jul 2017

- A project-driven mentoring platform built for experienced devs and learners to collaborate and grow.
- · Developed using Ruby on Rails and PostgreSQL.

Resource Wall Jun 2017 to Jun 2017

- Allow learners to save learning resources like tutorials, blogs and videos in a central place that is publicly available to any user.
- Developed using HTML, EJS, jQuery, AJAX, JavaScript and Sass in front-end, and Node, Express, PostgreSQL and Knex in back-end.

Employment

Salytics

Toronto, Canada Oct 2017 to Current

Technical Consultant

Oct 2017 to corre

- Created/updated project plan and status report, monitoring and controlling projects.
- Developed systems.
- Marketing automation tools: created landing pages, forms and emails, configured campaigns and programs on Eloqua, Marketo, Salesforce Marketing Cloud.

Supergasbras Project Analyst

Rio de Janeiro, Brazil Feb 2014 to Jun 2016

- Participated in the corporate PMO launching.
- Worked as team member of PMO group, supporting 7 projects simultaneously, within a program to ERP system implementation, to successful completion within the allocated time.
- Supported 10+ Project Managers in all aspects of the project lifecycle.

Supergasbras

Business Technology Analyst

Rio de Janeiro, Brazil Jun 2011 to Feb 2014

- Defined methodology and templates for software testing in Corporate IT.
- Led quality assurance of 5 softwares systems delivered by Corporate IT.
- Managed outsourced test team, including 4 professionals assigned in different projects.

Certifications

Salesforce Marketing Cloud Email Specialist

Marketo Certified Expert

PMI/PMP - Project Management Professional

BSTQB/CTFL - Certified Tester, Foundation Level